[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 2008 comedy, produced by Judd Apatow, stars Owen Wilson as a bodyguard, hired by a couple of high-school boys.", "correct_answer": "Drillbit Taylor", "incorrect_answers": ["Year One", "Step Brothers", "Pineapple Express"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which special type of wormwood, used exclusively for spicing, is one of the four fines herbes of French cooking?", "correct_answer": "Tarragon", "incorrect_answers": ["Rocket", "Sumac", "Mustard"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The movie Jeepers Creepers was released in 2002.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The 2007 film adaptation of the graphic novel 300 was shot in 60 days.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what area is Garys occupation on the 2006 movie The Break-Up?", "correct_answer": "Tour guide business", "incorrect_answers": ["Show business", "Art", "Law"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which US city is nicknamed The Venice of  America?", "correct_answer": "Fort Lauderdale, Florida", "incorrect_answers": ["Punta Gorda, Florida", "Key West, Florida", "Biloxi, Mississippi"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which actor played the sinister Gabriel Sylar Gray in the TV series Heroes?", "correct_answer": "Zachary Quinto", "incorrect_answers": ["Zachery Ty Bryan", "Zac Efron", "Zach Braff"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which movie are you watching if you hear In my classroom, poetry is its own reward?", "correct_answer": "Dangerous Minds", "incorrect_answers": ["Coach Carter", "Stomp The Yard", "The Substitute"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "At the end of the movie Arsenic and Old Lace the cab driver says he is what?", "correct_answer": "a coffee pot", "incorrect_answers": ["a priest", "a lunk head", "an unemployed cabbie"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "42 is a domino game popular in which part of the world?", "correct_answer": "Texas", "incorrect_answers": ["France", "Guatemala", "Hawaii"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This landlocked Alpine country, whose official Latin name is Confoederatio Helvetica, is a federation of relatively autonomous cantons.", "correct_answer": "Switzerland", "incorrect_answers": ["Austria", "Belgium", "Liechtenstein"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Hollywood actress turned down a role in Alfred Hitchcocks 1947 movie The Paradine Case?", "correct_answer": "Greta Garbo", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "Judy Garland", "Audrey Hepburn"]}]